### Privacy Policy

At Private VPN we abide by our No Log policy and stand by our commitment of user privacy and security. This Privacy policy explains privacy practices of Private VPN, what information we collect through your access, how we use such information and the security we provide for protecting such information. As the data controller for personal data, we administer the strictest policies in safeguarding your privacy and security and we try to collect as minimum information as we can, which is required to provide you with our Services.

### Secure your device

* How do we collect it?
* How do we use this information?
* How long wil we store your Personal information?

##### How do we collect the information?

**Directly from you:**

This data is collected when you take a subscription of one of our packages where we require that you provide personal information, such as an email address and payment information, in order to establish a Private VPN account, when you contact us via email, chat or social media platforms, or when you publicly leave a review on any platform.

**Our sites:**

This data we collect when you visit any of our website, our partner and affiliated sites, or interact with our adds.

**Our Apps:**

We collect htis data when you download our app and use it.

##### How do we use this information?

We collect this information to provide you with the best and personalized services that we will continuously improve according to your interests and requirements

* **Provisioning of Services:** To create your account, collect payment for our Services, verify your identity when you log into the Site, and administer accounts.
    
* **Improving our Products:** To better understand and monitor how our products and services are found, how visitors engage with them, provide visitors with relevant content or advertisements, identifying performance issues with our Site and app, improve them accordingly, fix bugs and maintain our products and services.
    
* **Commumications:** To send you information by emails, about payment transactions, links to site including password reset emails, product updates, changes to any of our Sites or Apps, to send you promotional offers that we think might interest you.
    
* **Personalize:** We monitor and analyze your profile, content that interests you and recent trends and customize the content we show you, including adds.
    
* **Save From Fraud:** Verify your identity and prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity.
    
* **Create Personal Data:** We may also create Personal Data about you, such as records of your interactions with our customer service department or details of your payments to us.
    
* **Others:** We use collected information from cookies and other technology to enhance our services and your experience using them.

##### How long will we store your Personal Information?

We keep your personal information for a certain period of time usually for maximum 2 years after you have stopped using Private VPN but usually depends on the purpose for keeping the data. If we are keeping your information to provide you services, we will discard it after 2 years of you not using Private VPN, company keeps your IP address as long as you are using Private VPN, just like that information used for improving and analyzing the performance and user experience is discarded when you delete the account. Personal information which is needed to communicate with users and provide customer support is processed for no longer than 2 years following the last communication with the exception of the device information (collected with your consent to solve your problems with the app), which we store for no longer than 7 days. We will not discard your data unless and until we are legally required to maintain it, for e.g. If you have outstanding credit, unresolved claim or theirs a fraud alert

**Disclosure:**

Private VPN uses your information for all the purposes listed above other then that we don't disclose any of your information to third parties under any circumstances. Any personal data related to Private VPN accounts is under the exclusive control of Private VPN only, including storage on equipment and servers that Private VPN own. Only, when necessary, for a certain time period, and for processing exclusively connected to the objectives and legitimate interests described in this Privacy Policy will this data need to be shared with other associated companies, while at all times maintaining the same data protection standards. We might need to transfer your personal data to a third party involved in a business transaction if our organizational structure changes (for example, if we go through a restructuring or are acquired), but we'll make sure that party has signed a contract limiting how your personal data is used to what's required for the transaction. Private VPN does not save users' originating IP addresses when they connect to our service, it is impossible to identify users when given our servers' IP addresses. Furthermore, since Private VPN does not save the applications, services, or websites that our users access while using our Services, we are unable to divulge this information

### Address

[\[email protected\]](https://privatevpn.app/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
  
[Hall Floor 2, China Center 2,  
Wallayat Complex, Near Bahria Town phase 7,  
Rawalpindi, Pakistan.](https://www.google.com/maps/place/9D+Technologies/@33.5334212,73.1101987,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x38dff3130623d8a5:0x7e2126a48b976d58!8m2!3d33.5334212!4d73.1123874?shorturl=1)

### Policies

### General

© 2022 Private VPN. All rights reserved.
